<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><docs>https://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><title>consultant on Pitch by Shun Kakinoki</title><link>https://pitch.shunkakinoki.com/tags/consultant/</link><description>Recent content in consultant on Pitch by Shun Kakinoki</description><ttl>1440</ttl><generator>Hugo 0.74.3</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright&amp;copy; Shun Kakinoki</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:59:16 UT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pitch.shunkakinoki.com/tags/consultant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Communication Consultant</title><link>https://pitch.shunkakinoki.com/014/</link><guid>https://pitch.shunkakinoki.com/014/</guid><description>AI Communication Consultant Mission Empower the world with the aid of your own private communication consultant
Problem Person-to-person communication is as important as ever, yet we do not have a systematic workflow to acquire it Increasingly more and more people are being judged by AI? Then shouldn&amp;rsquo;t the AI be in charge of training us too? People&amp;rsquo;s behaviors are not always rational in social opportunities Solution Affordable, Private, &amp;amp; Ubiquitous Private Communication Consultant Training with apps or AR/VR as a practice field Personal-training as a service pioneer -&amp;gt; 50 years later, would be still be organic as we are today?</description><category domain="https://pitch.shunkakinoki.com/categories/ai">Ai</category><content:encoded><![CDATA[AI Communication Consultant  Mission Empower the world with the aid of your own private communication consultant
 Problem  Person-to-person communication is as important as ever, yet we do not have a systematic workflow to acquire it Increasingly more and more people are being judged by AI? Then shouldn&amp;rsquo;t the AI be in charge of training us too? People&amp;rsquo;s behaviors are not always rational in social opportunities   Solution  Affordable, Private, &amp;amp; Ubiquitous Private Communication Consultant Training with apps or AR/VR as a practice field Personal-training as a service pioneer -&amp;gt; 50 years later, would be still be organic as we are today?  ]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>